Antonio Tejado 4 hours after the robbery of
Antonio tejado a las 4 horas del robo de
his aunt after that big scare in which he
su tía después de ese gran susto en el
found people in his house
que se encontró con gente en su casa
threatening her to open the
amenazándola para que le abriera las
safes and tell him where are the
cajas fuerte le dijera Dónde están las
valuables and so on appeared
cosas de valor y demás apareció
comforting me at the moment he showed
consolándome el momento le demostró
absolute concern to his aunt the
absoluta preocupación a su tía el
singer's nephew did not hesitate to be
sobrino de la cantante no dudó en ser
one of the first to appear at his
uno de los primeros en personarse en su
house He all the time tries to calm them down
casa Él todo el rato trata de calmarlas
comfort them of the Dachshund breed as he did so
consolarlos de raza tekel como jecho
that his aunt and her partner Imma Casal would
para que su tía y su pareja imma casal
have some joy after that hard
tuvieran una alegría tras ese duro
mishap the curious thing is that the puppy
percance lo curioso es que el perrito
would be from a litter that was raised by the girlfriend
sería de una camada que criaba la novia
of one of those arrested, that is, he took and
de uno de los detenidos o sea cogió y le
gave him the same day to his aunt a dog
regaló el mismo día a su tía un perro
that was in charge of raising the girlfriend of
que se encargaban de criar la novia de
one of those involved of those who
alguno de los implicados de los que
are detained very strongly
están detenidos muy fuerte